Let's start by giving quick singles,
Baba ji, tell me about your trends,
yes, good morning. The one I like right now
is ICICI General Insurance
and it should be available at 1141 in about 10-12 days.
Here the time is 1160. The
stop will be at 1135 ICICI General
Insurance and you should pay attention today at
40 on
ICICI. Okay, Prakashan's call will be
Rajesh Satpute ji, I will pick you.
I am keeping an eye on Aurobindo Pharma. I think
after the results there was a widening, but this
gap is getting filled. Currently
it is trading above 50 deg. So,
buy in and pharma, your stop loss should be
435 and as I said earlier,
75 480 is its target which is pending, so this
left-on deep strategy is available from this,
so it is on B
Pharma space, see my pharma space at 448 60,
what will be Mana Saheb's trick,
Virendra ji, see, PVR looks interesting
because here  Consolidation was being seen and the
new range was becoming stronger
but today somewhere a
break out was seen in PVR above ₹1700 on the intraday chart,
so we will
buy PVR at current levels and
your stop loss will be at 1684 or so but
look at the range up to 1775, let me go, okay, the
prices on PVR are good, the
market is up by almost 2% in a special movie, still around
5758. Below on Nifty, Ashish Chaturdashi, your
pic
[music]
looks good, we will turn it on, but this
stock has a proxy play to play the entire case
and if you look today, the technical is
very good, the break out of Poland flag has been
given by Vector Fruits at 512, I
think there is a very strong support of 490 here,
so one should buy this top from 490 test top,
56570. Please
note that the views given on Mani Control are the
personal views of the experts, the
website or the management is not responsible for it.
Mani Control recommends
consulting a certified expert before making any investment decisions.